Railway Labor Executives' Association Records 5484
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series XIII: Washington Job Protection Agreement, 1936-1963
  - Washington Job Protection Agreement, Union Pacific Railroad and Spokane International Railroad versus Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers and Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen [folder 2 of 3], 1962 (Box 185, Folder 10b)
  - Washington Job Protection Agreement, Union Pacific Railroad and Spokane International Railroad versus Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers and Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen [folder 3 of 3], 1962 (Box 185, Folder 10c)
- Series XIV: Oversize Materials
  This series contains oversize materials from the RLEA Office Files.
  - Government: ICC Accident Bulletin No. 132 for Calendar Year 1962, 1964 (Box 186, Folder 1)
    Bound Volume
  - Government: ICC Accident Bulletin No. 133 for Calendar Year 1963, 1965 (Box 186, Folder 2)
    Bound volume.